# KATELYN MICHALOVE

Senior Product Designer

katelynmichalove@gmail.com katelynmichalove.com

615-613-5617

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Sunbelt Rentals**

Senior Product Designer / May 2021 - Present Product Designer / Aug 2020 - May 2021 Junior Product Designer / July 2019 - Aug 2020

#### • Sunbeltrentals.com

Design lead for the complete redesign of Sunbelt Rentals' primary digital touch point. As a part of this effort, I conducted stakeholder interviews, user interviews, launched a customer survey, and took designs from wireframes to launch. As a result, we saw a 50% decrease in time to task and a 50% increase in online payments.

#### • Dispatch and Logistics Platform

Product redesign to identify inefficiencies and increase transportation profitability. This involved field interviews and observations, wireframing new solutions and features to solve dispatcher needs, utilizing and contributing to a design system, usability testing and iteration.

#### SmartEquip - iOS Mobile Inspection Application

1 Week sprint redesign to improve the user flows, match iOS HIG, and convert visual design to Sunbelt Rentals branding

#### Freelance / Product Designer

Aug 2018- Jul 2019

• Baseball analytics website to help launch a new business.

### **Procter and Gamble / Process Engineer**

Jun 2017 - Jul 2018

• Led troubleshooting for the chemical plant to solve for process improvement areas.

# **EDUCATION**

**University of Tennessee** / 2017 / BA Chemical Engineering

**Bloc** / 2019 / UX Design Apprenticeship

### **SUMMARY**

I am a Senior Product Designer with skills in conducting user research and leading projects from wireframe to launch. I am data-driven and seek out analytics, user research, and competitive insight to drive design decision. I collaborate with the team to define requirements and develop a product that solves users' problems while meeting business objectives.

### **TOOLS**

Sketch, Figma

Marvel, Invision

**Adobe Creative Suite** 

Dovetail

Lookback

Miro, Figjam

Survey Gizmo/Alchemer

Git, GitHub

Google Analytics

HTML, CSS

Jira, Confluence

## SKILL SET

User Experience Design

User Research

Market Research

**Usability Testing** 

Information Architecture

Visual Design

**Branding** 

**Prototyping** 

Frontend Development